A lot of business gurus can be guilty of
telling, telling, telling.
This is how you make millions. This
is how you make 10 grand a flipping
minute,
whatever it is.
But not many people show you.
And in this video,
I'm going to show you through four
different businesses, three
of which applied using the link in the
description.
So if any of you run an online business
and you want me to just have a little look
over your content, your sales process,
whatever, I'll happily do it.
Use that link, apply, throw in your name.
I'll get round to it as soon as I can.
The first one that came up
was slightly different to much
that I've seen before.
Side Hustle SU, Amazon FBA expert.
I'm not going to lie to you,
I had to Google what FBA meant.
And this is a little problem
that I've faced.
I've been working in online business for
years, but yesterday, embarrassingly, I
had to Google what e-commerce meant.
Everyone's out there like, "Yeah,
I made my wealth in e-commerce.
I've made tens of millions." I was like,
"What the fuck is e-commerce?" Turns out
it's just a posh way to say you're buying
and selling stuff online.
And I was like,
why make this more difficult than we need
to?
So first thing here,
you're an Amazon FBA expert.
I had to Google what that was.
I don't know what FBA is, and it's like
dropshipping, but you actually pay for it,
and then you send the stock.
So it'd be a bit like
when we send Nootonic to Amazon, or
when we send it to
TikTok shop. And those,
for any of you that don't know,
are the caffeine-free
sachets, which go well
when you're having a coffee in the
morning.
I'll put a link to those in the
description as well.
And on a quick side tangent,
I asked ChatGPT what it thought of
Nootonic's blend
earlier on,
and it gave it a 9.5 out of 10.
Now,
I help Muslims make 10,000 pounds a month
with Amazon FBA.
Cool.
But I'm just going to throw this out here.
Why just Muslims? I get it.
You're a Muslim. Salam Alaikum. Wallahi,
brother.
People do love people that
are similar to them.
If someone drives the same car as you,
you see them,
you're going to let them out.
Oh, that guy's got a Golf R.
I've got a Golf R. Let them out.
Same way that if you're on holiday,
you find out someone's from the same area,
you're suddenly best friends.
Someone's like, "Yeah,
I'm from South London." You're
like, "Okay, you mean Croydon?
Let's go out tonight
and stab someone." That's a
joke.
People that have been to Croydon will
know. They'll find it funny.
So I just feel like
if you're an Amazon FBA expert,
why just help Muslims?
Because chances are, if you
were to just help everyone,
80% of your clientele are
going to be Muslims because of your
appearance.
You have the beard with the trimmed
mustache.
I actually Googled this the other day,
or I asked ChatGPT about it because Islam
Makhachev, Atal, them Dagestanis,
they've all got the same kind of
appearance.
I wanted to know culturally what
that meant.
So maybe even the mission statement is,
I help people make money online using
Amazon. And I just think
that although maybe not wanting to work
with
non-Muslims is completely fine.
It's your prerogative.
There could be a wider market,
and I just think
that sometimes there can be an
element of cringe factor where
when people are like,
"I help lesbians lose fat,"
you're like,
is their sexuality really a big pivotal
part of whether or not
you can help them? I'm not sure.
And the same with religion.
Just because you're Muslim,
I'm not sure that means you can't help me.
So just throwing it out there. And again,
this is your choice, your prerogative.
But from a business perspective,
if someone's like, "James,
I've got a business.
I'm a Mormon.
I'm going to help other Mormons get in
shape," I'd be like, "Let's
help all people get in shape.
It's a bigger market.
So let's have a look at your content."
To find beauty suppliers, this one is-
Very niche, too niche.
The majority of the internet
are going to be like, "What are
you on about?"
99% of you are going to fail starting an
online business, and here's why.
You don't know how to launch a product.
You don't know how to build a website.
You don't want to show your face.
The one thing that content creation gurus
will
not tell you,
most of them don't actually do the
business that they teach.
So considering you're a young guy,
aspirational, making money,
selling stuff online, I think
that should be the play in the content.
Now, you call yourself Side Hustle SU,
so it'd be great if you just sit here
and be
like, "This behind me
is my side hustle."
And they'd look at all the boxes and be
like, "Oh, what's that? What's
that side hustle?"
And it generates me X per month.
Throw up a screenshot of how much you're
making.
If you're someone
that wants to work for yourself
or create a side hustle that can
give you whatever income,
let me tell you how I would do it starting
off.
And then a lot of this should play into
that.
Like,
you've got all these boxes behind you.
Use this as a visual hook.
All these things behind me are orders
that I'm going to sell over the next week.
Let me explain to you how this works.
If I had 1,000 pounds to start a side
hustle, this is exactly what
I would do.
So again,
this one should be maybe even a story.
If you have a client, this is Dave.
He only had 1,000 pounds to invest.
I got him to do this, and this
is the result he got.
And if you want to get the same result as
Dave, then you can do whatever.
Up here, I feel like this
is maybe a little bit cluttered.
We should take out the seven-figure
seller, 100 people helped.
Delete that,
and then suddenly we won't have to click
to populate this.
Free Amazon guide. We're going through.
What are we going to get?
Oh, for some reason, let's not have
that as italic.
It makes it hard to read,
but maybe I'm just old and going blind.
This could be a lot simpler.
So maybe even delete that.
And this bit here,
this free video reveals how complete
beginners are making their
first sales in 30 days or less.
This bit of copy here
is stronger than this one,
because this one's about hmm, yeah.
And this I don't really understand.
I'd rather see a Stripe payment.
It's quite universal. Cool.
So that's my advice here. Now,
when I'm looking down at your
content, let's have a little look.
I'm not really seeing many outliers from
that 700 view mark. Oh, here we go.
A million views.
Have you ever tried to do nothing
but felt overwhelmed by the crowd?
Okay, so this angle, maybe we use again.
The casual iPhone in hand, hit record.
He's out and about. Love to see it.
Maybe this is something
that people like to see.
My only concern here is-
You can barely move. There's pushing,
there's-
And again,
I'm saying this from a place of as much
respect as possible.
If you're making posts that
are to do with your religion, which is
absolutely fine,
sometimes you can attract people
that just don't want anything
to do with your FBA business.
And although it's great here
that these kind of posts
are going to bolster engagement
or whatever, we need to try
and stay in line with
the business and sometimes ask ourself,
is this post beneficial to the business?
Because if you draw in a load of people
that don't have the
interest in the topics you're talking
about,
you are growing a subprime audience.
And as someone that's grown many subprime
audiences before, it can be frustrating.
It's why on my business channel,
even this channel,
I know how to make viral
YouTube videos,
but I don't make them on this business
channel because if they go
viral,
I'm going to attract a load of people
that just aren't interested in doing
business with me.
It's going to ruin my click-through rates,
ruin my conversions,
ruin everything.
So maybe let's just make it all about FBA,
whatever that
is.
Let's make it all about selling on Amazon,
and let's just try to not make it,
at the same time,
like a Muslim exclusive hangout group,
because
I think there are so many young people
that you could help that maybe aren't from
the same religious background. Moving on.
Finn Stewart,
I help people speak English with
confidence.
This is a great title here,
but this picture, brother,
this picture needs a bit
of work.
Everyone uses this thing called PFP Maker.
You go to pfpmaker.com.
You can make a nice picture.
That's where me, Chris Bloomeson,
everyone else do theirs.
Okay, so the concern I have here
is 60,000 followers averaging less than
10% per reel. What happened?
What happened?
I'm not saying you bought them.
Did you buy them? What happened?
I'm running out of eggs. It is what it is.
They-
So the problem here is, one,
this microphone is a really,
really cheap microphone.
It's like 15 pounds. Let me have a look.
If I quite literally type in cheap
wireless microphone.
Boom. There it is.
The Didier dog shit microphone.
It's fucking 15 quid, mate.
No wonder it sounds like p-Shit.
These Hollylands are amazing.
You'll see Gary Vee and Hormozi using
them, and DJI mics.
Your literal profession is in
helping people speak and sound better,
yet you are
skimping on your audio quality, which
is hypocritical, my friend.
Now, my issue here is if people know you,
then when you start a reel, they know
what's going on.
Don't mind, doesn't matter.
So imagine I've never seen you before.
I don't know you're an English teacher.
I've got no flipping idea what's going on,
and I'm just scrolling the internet, and
I see this.
Don't mind, doesn't matter.
Sorry. What?
Me too. So-
What?
You're just a very well-spoken English
lad, talking very posh,
saying random things
British
And I'm scrolling away as fast as I can
because this is just a bit weird.
Which sentence is correct?
That's a better one because at least this
one starts with a hook.
Now, you've got an impeccable hairline,
brother. Good-looking lad.
Look at those curls. Well,
a weird little thing up here.
Bit of a strange place to film.
But we almost need to preface every single
video
with what is happening,
because nine out of 10 people watching
this may not follow
you or be watching. So-
What's this called?
People are like, "What's wrong with you,
mate?
It's called a fucking toilet,
you weirdo." So even if everything says,
"If you want
to speak perfect English, hit support
and you appreciate," boom.
Because then if you want to speak perfect
English, foreign audiences are like,
"Yes, I do." And English people go,
"I'm just not interested in an English
lesson
off you,
sir." Now let's look for some outliers.
See,
not many of these have really nudged past
the mark.
This one here.
Repeat after me. Her.
Her, here, hear, hur, her. Great.
So this one outperformed all the others
by threefold.
So this should've been replicated in the
next few reels to see
if there was a content bucket here.
Because if the repeat after me bucket
works, we should have really tried
to emulate that again to see whether
or not it was, or it was just a fluke.
And that's really what I need you to do.
I need you to start changing up the
content system, get a proper microphone,
put
the fucking spatula away because it's
funny, it's quirky,
but then after I've seen
it five times, I'm like, "Mate." And yeah,
then try and find out what works and
double down on it. But to me, no offense,
it just looks like you're putting out
loads of stuff that isn't working.
And instead of changing it around... Oh,
104.
To fool someone. To mug off. Friend. Mate.
Young.
Okay. English with Finn. So this guy,
you need to collab with this guy as
often as you bloody can, mate,
because this one went bloody bananas.
You should pay that person,
get them to spend the day,
fly out to wherever they
are, because all of these
are getting such minimal effort compared
to this.
You need to repeat this as many times as
you can. Let's have a look here.
Oh, I hate this. Just have one thing, bro.
Just have one thing.
If I said to you,
"Which one of these do you want me to
click?" You'd say, "Oh, put
that one then." One-to-one English
coaching. Please don't be a typeform.
Please don't be a typeform.
Please don't be a... Oh,
that picture's a bit big.
Wouldn't it be great to have a native
teacher at your fingertips?
It'd be nice to have an image a little bit
smaller than that. Okay.
This is not a well-laid-out page. Look,
I've got to go all the way down here
to find out how much it is.
A good created landing page would take me
on a bit more
of a journey. I tell you what,
I actually saw a landing page
yesterday. I know exactly where it
is because I actually do
all of this. Noor. Where is she? Noor.
Yes. Okay.
This young lady created this as a landing
page, and I was like, "This is great."
First of all, it's hosted on Leadpages,
which I love. Big fan of Leadpages.
She's got a bit of branding up here,
which could have gone,
but we'll keep it there
anyway. The Business X-ray. I was like,
"Oh, do you know what?
That's a great term." Straight away,
I know exactly what's going on.
A business X-ray,
you're just going to scan a business
and look into it.
You don't need another course or tool.
You need someone to look under the hood
and tell you what the hell is going on,
how
to fix it. Wow, what a title, Noor.
This is amazing. Love it.
We've got a nice VSL here.
Your business looks successful on the
outside, but behind-
That audio is crisp. It's amazing
... the scenes,
it's barely holding together.
Your team needs you.
Operations are messy.
Fantastic. Look at this.
I want to X-ray my business.
Imagine this. What a great use of copy.
You start working,
"Oh my God." What you can expect.
Who's this for?
Oh my God.
Look at this little Buy now button.
Take me to stripe. Take me to...
Yes. Love it. Love it. Beautiful.
Fantastic.
So then when we see that,
and we come back, you know what I mean,
brother?
It's just all over the place. Email me,
start here.
It needs a bit of work, bro,
but it's all right.
Private classes and my team,
this just scattered me.
Give us one link,
and you can go to Bitly
and clean this up or get something.
It's a bit crazy. Bit much going on.
But you clean it up,
I'm sure you'd be flying.
Now, this next one,
saw it in the applications,
and I have no idea what's going on.
It said The Chicken Rush. What?
The Chicken Rush. 10,000 followers,
though.
Let's have a little look.
Can I ask what we're doing? Yes. Well,
I'm being hunted.
We run a game where someone dresses up as
a chicken and hides, and we're running
our own- Oh my God. Okay, cool.
And we're live.
This is amazing.
Thank you guys again. Here we go.
So we're in the Phoenix Pub today, one
of the best pubs in Soho.
It serves a Goli, Scol,
Scol, Tolly, one of the better ciders.
If there can be a good cider.
There are. 3 hours,
41 minutes.
How do you think it's going so far?
Well, nothing's crashed yet.
[upbeat music] I'm not hating the music.
Seven out of 10.
So you dress as a chicken,
and people have got to find you.
This is how we played the ultimate game of
hide and seek in the Italian Alps.
First-
This is incredible
This is how I got 100 people to chase a
chicken around London.
First,
I spent a whole year building an app
that can be used to play hide and seek
in big cities.
I love it. Okay, let's have a look.
Day two of people hunting me in a chicken
costume.
These hooks are incredible because we're
trying to figure out what's going on.
And they can win 200 pounds. Hey, hey,
hello.
I'm hiding in a pub or bar,
and we just published this map online.
It shows a huge circle around London,
and every five minutes, this is going to
shrink around my hiding spot.
Because no one found us last time,
today's prize is
200 pounds.
Hamilton Hall from Wetherspoons.
We have found ourselves a tiny place to
hide. A naga curry.
I hate-
This is fantastic
For the next two hours and 35 minutes,
the chicken will be hiding in a pub or bar
somewhere in London. Today,
the first person to find me receives 100
pounds in cash. There-
Great. I love this. This is amazing.
I think this is really good.
The chicken can now see hunting teams on
the map. Wow, okay.
Now, how does this business model work?
Do people pay to be a part of it?
I don't even know. But do you know what?
Love the concept. Originality, love it.
Really clean here. Chase that chicken.
More info. Okay.
Hide and seek reimagined. Enter website.
100 pound hunt. Blind dates.
What's this? Oh, typeforms.
Blind dates to do with chicken.
That's interesting How to play.
This landing page is fantastic.
How to play. General corporate.
I love the little click-through there as
well.
Gather the squad. Get a group of eight
or more together. Chicken select.
This is so cool. I love this.
I'd love to know how you came up with the
concept of this. This is great.
So these reels here, 200, 200,
1.3 million.
She should double down on the content
and just keep doing this and
keep telling stories
and getting it on TikTok.
And you belong on "Dragons" then.
That's what I'm saying. This is amazing.
Okay, the last thing we're going to do
is someone in my mentorship
created a flyer, and I hated it.
I absolutely hated it.
How dare you create such a disgusting
flyer?
So the problem is here,
"Claim two free 45-minute personal
training sessions at
Ran-" No one wants a free personal
training session.
It's like when people say,
"Join my email newsletter." No one woke up
today wanting
an email newsletter, brother. "My name
is Kareem, and I'm partnering with my
facility..." This is some copy
that I've kind of given him.
"My name is Kareem." Bro,
you're in your late 20s.
You don't need to tell people, okay?
You don't need to tell people.
All right, you just say,
"I'm Kareem." Let's go into ChatGPT to
begin.
Okay, this will do. Let's give this a go.
Using this image,
can you please give me a template for a
flyer I could hand out? It's portrait,
two sides, please, and I
want no text.
I am going to overlay the text
myself.
I could probably do this in Photoshop
anyway, but I thought, why not?
Let's give this a little go. What
is going on with ChatGPT today?
Mate, you are a fucking knob sometimes.
Yeah.
So really, all we need
is maybe we'll try
and color match from that
purple.
Maybe we even just put a little box across
here. Fine.
Let's think of something maybe original.
There's nothing worse than a personal
trainer interrupting your workout.
So instead,
I've carefully selected the local
best-kept
gardens to let you know an offer I have
for you.
Then maybe we go,
a little please turn over.
So we can maybe have this as side one,
and this is something that we can
send to a designer because I'm not a
designer.
Just thinking about some kind of ways we
could be a little bit more creative.
Kareem one. So maybe on the other side,
we... Or is it anytime?
Let's try and find something
that looks pretty good.
And remember, at any point,
if you want to get a critique, there
is a link in the
description below. Then really simply,
just going to take this out,
maybe bring in
the picture of the gym. Oh,
it's a bit annoying that
that Ranwick color's a little
bit out, isn't it, for this side?
We'll get, we'll take this.
We'll get rid of that rectangle, won't we?
I'm Kareem.
I'm partnering my free introduction gym
walkthrough and
two 45-minute sessions. Okay,
we probably have to make this text a
little bit
smaller, aren't we?
Two of your sessions to welcome you into
our club.
So something here,
free introduction gym walkthrough,
and two 45-minute
sessions. For a personal trainer,
the truth is, if you do these for free
and you
actually genuinely want to help people,
some people are just going to end up
going,
"Do you know what? You're a nice lad.
Let's do some training sessions." We can
now-- we're just going to take this one as
an example, and then maybe even scan this.
Real rough.
Then let's go Kareem 2. Sweet.
Copy to send
to a designer to mock up for you.
Any issues with the
copy, let me know. I know the purples
are out.
And then, in essence,
there's nothing worse than a personal
trainer interrupting
your workout. So instead,
I've carefully selected the local area's
best-kept
gardens to let you know about an offer I
have for you. I'm Kareem.
I'm partnering with the AF facility in
Ranwick to offer you a free introduction
gym
walkthrough,
and two 45-minute sessions to welcome you
into our club.
No hidden catches.
Scan this to contact me.
I think that's just nice.
You think that where we've come from was,
"My name is Kareem, and I'm partnering my
facility to help people become familiar
around free weights and gym equipment.
It's really simple.
You reach out to me on this, mention
that you get one of those
flyers, we can book. Hey,
I hope to..." Yeah,
then we just clean that up.
For me, I think flyers are not dead.
I think they've still got quite a lot of
potential if you do them right.
And one thing that I think
is going to come back
is fake parking tickets, but
we'll do that in another video.
So there's some insights into what I would
do into
those several kind of business problems.
If you want to apply,
there'll be a link in the description.
If you want to work with me,
I'll put a link to that there.
And if you haven't tried Neutonic yet,
definitely try getting some of that.
Bosch.